We're getting strafed, shelled, bombed, and blasted.
And it isn't even our damned war!
Go Tell the Spartans is a war film directed by Ted Post.
A unit of American military advisors in Vietnam prior to the major U.S.
involvement finds similarities between their helpless struggle against the Viet Cong and
the doomed actions of a French unit at the same site a decade before.
Maj. Asa Barker, played by Burt Lancaster.
Cpl. Courcey, played by Craig Wasson.
Capt. Alfred Olivetti, played by Marc Singer.
Lt. Raymond Hamilton, played by Joe Unger.
Lt. Finley Wattsberg, played by David Clennon.
Cowboy, played by Evan C. Kim.
Go Tell the Spartans is a 1978 American war film directed
by Ted Post and starring Burt Lancaster.
The film is based on Daniel Ford's 1967 novel Incident at Muc Wa about U.S.
Army military advisors during the early part of the Vietnam War in 1964,
when Ford was a correspondent in Vietnam for The Nation.
The film explores themes of vietnam war, vietnam,
based on novel or book, major, 1960s.